module.exports = [
  {
    question: `KABUL`,
    answer: 'AFGHANISTAN',
    next: 1
  },
  {
    question: 'BRUSSELS',
    answer: 'BELGIUM',
    next: 2
  },
  {
    question: 'SUCRE',
    answer: 'BOLIVIA',
    next: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'OTTAWA',
    answer: 'CANADA',
    next: 4
  },
  {
    question: 'SANTIAGO',
    answer: 'CHILE',
    next: 5
  },
  {
    question: 'QUITO',
    answer: 'ECUADOR',
    next: 6
  },
  {
    question: 'CAIRO',
    answer: 'EGYPT',
    next: 7
  },
  {
    question: 'SUVA',
    answer: 'FIJI',
    next: 8
  },
  {
    question: 'HELSINKI',
    answer: 'FINLAND',
    next: 9
  },
  {
    question: 'ATHENS',
    answer: 'GREECE',
    next: 10
  },
  {
    question: 'GEORGETOWN',
    answer: 'GUYANA',
    next: 11
  },
  {
    question: 'BAGHDAD',
    answer: 'IRAQ',
    next: 12
  },
  {
    question: 'TOKYO',
    answer: 'JAPAN',
    next: 13
  },
  {
    question: 'BEIRUT',
    answer: 'LEBANON',
    next: 14
  },
  {
    question: 'VILNIUS',
    answer: 'LITHUANIA',
    next: 15
  },
  {
    question: 'MONACO',
    answer: 'MONACO',
    next: 16
  },
  {
    question: 'ISLAMABAD',
    answer: 'PAKISTAN',
    next: 17
  },
  {
    question: 'MOSCOW',
    answer: 'RUSSIA	',
    next: 18
  },
  {
    question: 'RIYADH',
    answer: 'SAUDI ARABIA',
    next: 19
  },
  {
    question: 'VICTORIA',
    answer: 'SEYCHELLES',
    next: 20
  },
  {
    question: '	LJUBLJANA',
    answer: 'SLOVENIA',
    next: 21
  },
  {
    question: 'MADRID',
    answer: 'SPAIN',
    next: 23
  },
  {
    question: 'DUSHANBE',
    answer: 'TAJIKISTAN',
    next:24
  },
  {
    question: 'WASHINGTON, D.C.',
    answer: 'UNITED STATES',
    next: 25
  },
  {
    question: 'ROME',
    answer: 'ITALY',
    next: 26
  },
  {
    question: 'SOFIA',
    answer: 'BULGARIA',
    next: 27
  },
  {
    question: 'VIENNA',
    answer: 'AUSTRIA',
    next: 28
  },
  {
    question: 'ALGIERS',
    answer: 'ALGERIA',
    next: 29
  },
  {
    question: 'BUENOS AIRES',
    answer: 'ARGENTINA',
    next: null
  },
];